(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 1,
"subtitles": 2
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
Perfume Remix by
The Gravy Navy
Ow!
Huh!
Come chase me.
HIT ME UP
Lyrics: KiRA / monii | Music: KiRA / monii / Johnny R.
Every day I spring-cleaning but
almost love's turned complicated
On the way up my heart got torn up
shredded all but deadened
Now they say I, I'm just a masochist or sick of it
Boy take a hint, you ain't gon' ever get this
Pedal to the metal shooting straight to the stars
Got a craving like a danger on the edge
she liked that, liked that, liked that
Up another level, sensation you just can't deny
Come get a taste, but can't say I won't bite
Supersonic I'm heading up I'm gonna (Oh-oh-oh-oh)
In my eyes Nirvana (Oh, I'm taking)
Pushing for the high, my lover, I gotta (Run-run-run-run)
But it's fun to see you try
So hit me up, off the map
I'ma take it all, my energy
Speeding up, fast ready, target lock
So hit me up, hit the dash
I'm a grader, and you wanna be
So hit me up, I'll never stop
In a new territory, I'm on the edge of glory
Boy just watch out, give me that rush
Got no regrets in my mind, boy don't lose the time
So hit me up, I'll turn the volume up, you got a crush
Such a cliché, you're a bad boy charm
better fall right back in your arms
Wasn't enough, you needed more
now you're begging to let you score
Sure you'll take it all in stride, oh I'm busy tonight
Goodbye, goodbye, gotta leave you dry
Always tryna play it cool, 20/20 vision on me
Just outside my field of view
yes she liked that, liked that, liked that
Engine booming, that's my cue, catch me if you can
You better keep up the chase, boy you falling behind
Supersonic I'm heading up I'm gonna (Oh-oh-oh-oh)
In my eyes Nirvana (Oh, I'm taking)
Pushing for the high, my lover, I gotta (Run-run-run-run)
But it's fun to see you try
HIT ME UP
Fun to see you try
Center of the map, I'ma take it all my energy
Speeding up fast, ready, tag along
Head to dash, I'm a-grade and you wanna be this
So hit me up, ah, and never stop
In a new territory, I'm on the edge of glory,
boy, just watch how I move, gimme that rush
Got no regrets on my mind,
but it's on you this time to hit me up,
on the loud volume up, you've got a crush
Ah, just barely wasn't enough, you should've
Ah, given me all that you got, you could've
Coming full circle, I hit a nerve, oh
Top spot's getting hot, watch me run it
So hit me up, rev it up and make that vroom vroom
When I hit you with that zoom zoom zoom zoom
If you know what's good for you, ooh ooh ooh
Fuel me now, I'm back in charge right now after dark
Yay! Kikiriki!
Welcome to my birthday in 2025!
Woohoo!
お誕生日です、私の
It's my birthday.
なんと、なんと、何歳になってるんでしょう、この不死鳥。
And, and, how old is this phoenix now?
It is my birthday. It is a very special occasion.
It is not just my birthday,
it is also the Super Special Summer!
We will make it a Super Special Summer today. Yes, yes!
And if you guys want, I have a hashtag up here, so please make use of it.
It is #KiaraBDay2025!
So post it all over social media.
Screenshots, or gifs, or jifs, whatever you want.
Share it to the world, spread the Wah-Wah-Love!
Thank you already in advance.
We started with the first song with KIRA's "HIT ME UP".
KIRA, another banger from my good friend KIRA.
Thank you for providing the world with bangers.
I'm taking them for myself. Hehe. They're mine now.
Yeah, that was fun. And did you like the little spicy dance? Hehe.
Let's take a little look at the stage. ステージも見ましょうか。
Let's take a little look at the stage. Let's look at the stage too.
Well, besides the Super Special Summer logo, we have some presents.
I wonder what's inside. And some balloons.
Maybe I'm gonna pop them when I'm done here. Hehe.
Yes! And then besides that, today, you know why it's so special?
Well, because we're gonna have super special merch at the end.
We're gonna have super special outside guests!
Ah! I never had an outside guest before. Exciting!
And, and, and... super special song reveal? Hmm.
Yeah, yeah, probably. You know me.
So please watch until the very end.
最後まで見てください。
Please watch until the end.
特別なサプライズいっぱいありますから。よろしくお願いします。
There are many special surprises. Please look forward to it.
Please listen to the next song, "UNDEAD".
UNDEAD (English Version)
I'm unhappy! If you're feeling over lot of woes
Then you better listen very close
Keep on trying, never give up, don't forget that's your life
The prospect of then running from the boring future yet to come
So counseling you, oh my, oh my, I'm unhappy piece of cake, yeah
UNDEAD (English Version)
Lyrics - Music: Ayase
Translation: Konnie Aoki
I'm unhappy!
Be happy! UNDEAD! UNDEAD!
Hey hey hey hey, somehow feeling like there's a fight within and it's been going on so long
And I'm feeling that I don't even want to show that version of me, of me, of me
And those figures of the old transparent ghosts over my route
The childish and painful memories have the deepest roots
Nowhere to be seen, way better than irony
They all see the me of the past when looking at me now
Labels I can't erase, in essence a common place
It's almost like something possessing me, it is wrapping 'round
And when loose, it's bound to self I used to be before
UNDEAD! Still alive!
Break the chain of your own catastrophe as I will still always embrace you in changes on and on
Don't settle for unhappiness, don't keep those eyes in stress
Now is the time to seize the joy and be happy with power
Oh, this whole world is one of, one of fantasy
Who knows what is coming up next, a monster or a snake?
This is the story starting after that encounter finally
With people or monstrous spirits, that's happy piece of cake, yeah
Past and future, can't change the past. Past and future, run for the future
Cutting in, somehow feeling like there's nothing to be looking forward to
A hope of time cannot be defined, that's how I'm feeling inside
There's nothing left if you live long enough, nothing is new
No sign of anything wonderful waiting down the line
Too much knowledge results in feeling like everything is but an unavoidable fate
Running revolution, fearless what I really want now
Like a dance to fresh ends
This is the way to guidance through
Reshaping compliance too, it's like I'm going under a lift
I consume everything
This one or that one or whichever
And now it all just stays the same
I'm still alive, time is a shade of your own path
In any era you pass by
Your future are fixed at this very moment
Fulfill the life you're set up for
And you believe keep moving on
Go for that happy ending
I'm still alive, I'm telling this to you now
So never give up on pursuing your happiness, keep it close to you now
Seeing only the suffering
Always enduring everything
It's almost as if you're dead or alive, which is it after all?
If you're doing your very best now
Then you gotta listen very close
Keep on trying never give up, be aware that you're alive
Drowning deep in unhappiness, or feeling that you're happiness
It's only, only, it's all on you
Universe all-embracing
All creation peace be with you yeah
Past
And future
Can't change the past
Past
And future
Run for the future
Where people gather and go, you'll find your worries and woes
So you gotta listen to this now
Monsters everywhere you can see
Oh RISE UP! PIKKAN! RISE UP! PIKKAN!
Oh RISE UP! PIKKAN! (ビッカーン！ビッカーン！)
Oh RISE UP! PIKKAN! (Pikkan! Pikkan!)
Oh RISE UP! PIKKAN!
いっしょになって 輝け Ready
Together, let's shine! Ready
3, 2, 1, AH!
さあ大好物のサマー
Now, it's our favorite summer
The only in my head Let's go!
もう逃げても無理そう 凸凹な答え Let's go!
No use running anymore, a bumpy answer Let's go!
やっちゃえピッカーン！
Go for it, Pikkan!
かっちゃえピッカーン！
Win it, Pikkan!
ファッションバデー
Fashion body
失敗じゃない 最低もない
Not a failure, not even rock bottom
祭典まで追いかけてけ
Keep chasing until the festival
混ぜられた想いが あえあえ僕を 独創する
Mixed feelings make me creative, oh yeah
出会いとはこれ 重なる囁き
This is an encounter, overlapping whispers
研ぎ澄ませていこう
Let's sharpen them
Oh RISE UP! PIKKAN! RISE UP! PIKKAN!
Oh RISE UP! PIKKAN! 変えていこうよ正々堂々さあ
Oh RISE UP! PIKKAN! Let's change it fair and square, now
Oh RISE UP! PIKKAN! RISE UP! PIKKAN!
いっしょになって 輝け Ready
Together, let's shine! Ready
3, 2, 1, AH!
イェー 最高だぜ この上ないのさ Top of buddy
Yeah! It's the best! There's nothing like it, Top of buddy
あっという間に上がれる 限界 Yeah
Rising up in the blink of an eye, the limit Yeah
Wow 何回だって立って晴れ
Wow, stand up as many times as it takes, it's sunny
傘なんていらないや雨
No need for an umbrella even if it rains
わいわい Don't you dare つかもうぜ
Wait, wait, Don't you dare! Let's grab it
もう一回やってやろうぜ！
Let's do it one more time!
メーデー 助けば問題ないね
Mayday, there's no problem if we help each other
星空にみる希望 明日も君と旅するでしょう
Hope seen in the starry sky, tomorrow I'll journey with you too
約束がちゃんと待ってるんだ OK!
The promise is waiting for us, OK!
エー 悲しみから泣くのは あえあえもうやめよう 弱くない
Eh, let's stop crying from sadness, oh yeah, we're not weak
乗り越えた壁 負けない強さ
The wall we overcame, the strength to not lose
研ぎ澄ませていこう
Let's sharpen it
RISE UP! Make it 抜群 ステキなガイ
RISE UP! Make it outstanding, a wonderful guy
RISE UP! Make it 爆走 待ちわびた合図とエール
RISE UP! Make it dashing, the long-awaited signal and cheer
叶え 3, 2, 1 Ready... AH!
Come true 3, 2, 1 Ready... AH!
僕らの場面 選ぼう 限界越え Go Let's go!
Let's choose our scene, beyond the limit, Go Let's go!
半端じゃない 燃えてる想いは上昇中
It's no joke, the burning feelings are on the rise
埋もれる感傷は 君の消しゴムで消してほしい
I want your eraser to erase the buried sentiment
期待は好きなだけ 全部僕らのため
Expect as much as you like, it's all for us
RISE UP! Make it 抜群 ステキなガイ
RISE UP! Make it outstanding, a wonderful guy
RISE UP! Make it 爆走 待ちわびた合図とエール
RISE UP! Make it dashing, the long-awaited signal and cheer
叶え 3, 2, 1 Ready... AH!
Come true 3, 2, 1 Ready... AH!
僕らの場面 選ぼう 限界越え Go Let's go!
Let's choose our scene, beyond the limit, Go Let's go!
A!
ホテルジャーニー その向こうに Hops together
Hotel journey, beyond that, Hops together
Come on Rise up! Rise up! Rise up!
Come on Rise up!
変えていこうよ正々堂々さあ
Let's change it fair and square, now
Oh RISE UP! PIKKAN! RISE UP! PIKKAN!
Okay, okay, okay!
Let's do self-introduction,
Let's do self-introductions,
even though they don't really need one.
Let's start with the senpai.
Yay!
ハロー！5期生桃鈴ねねねー！
Hello! 5th Gen, Momosuzu Nene-ne!
Fifthじゃなかったっけ？Fifth。
Wasn't it "Fifth"? Fifth.
Fifus! ね！
Fifus! Right!
フィフスジェネレーション！
Fifth Generation!
Yay!
と、後輩。
And, the kohai.
Hello!
HoloX、風真いろはでござる！
HoloX's Kazama Iroha de gozaru!
Yay!
でもあんまり英語入ってなかった気がする。
But I feel like there wasn't much English in that.
There wasn't enough English!
Very very so-so... sorry! 海外ニキ！
Very very so-so... sorry! Overseas Nikki!
It's been a while! 久しぶりだね。
It's been a while! It's been a long time.
It's been a while! It's been a while!
Two years? Maybe two years...
...that we danced together.
...since we danced together.
Long time ago! Long time ago!
寂しかったよ。
I missed you.
And Iroha-chan, good time! Last year, I think...
And Iroha-chan, good times! Last year, I think...
...last year. Yeah, happy, happy, happy!
...it was last year. Yeah, happy, happy, happy!
I feel like our colors match very well, right?
So maybe if Nene-chi is in the middle...
...look! Gradation! Gradation!
Yay!
Blonde, Pink, Orange. Beautiful!
Beautiful! 目の色、目の色。
Beautiful! Eye colors, eye colors.
あ、確か、いろはちゃん...
Ah, for sure, Iroha-chan...
Eye color...
...in my hair.
Yes, yes, yes, yes! Beautiful!
シナジーを感じる。ということで...
I feel the synergy. So...
The song we just sang together...
...we cannot say too clearly what it was all about,
but did you see this pose here? Hmm?
ポーズ！
Pose!
What is this pose? I wonder.
We're holding some kind of ball here,
but it could also very well be baseball?
野球？野球？
Baseball? Baseball?
ということで、I want everybody
So, I want everybody
to show me an original throwing pose. Okay?
Okay, okay!
イケイケスロー！
A cool throw!
Yes, yes! Okay!
カッコいいスロー、可愛い、なんでもOkay。
A cool throw, cute, anything is okay.
I start, okay? I start.
I'll start, okay? I'll start.
Here we go. Ball throwing challenge!
Three, two, one!
Hoi! Hoi!
カッコいい！
So cool!
Sexy! カッコいい！Sexy!
Sexy! Cool! Sexy!
Okay, okay! Next-o!
Okay, okay! Next up!
誰、誰？Who wants to do?
Who's next? Who wants to do it?
ねね！ねね！ねね！
Nene! Nene! Nene!
見る、見る、見る！Let's go!
Watching, watching, watching! Let's go!
イケイケ... うーん...
Cool... hmm...
飛んだ！ふん！
It flew! Hum!
Ah! Body-body throw! Body-body!
Body-body-chan! Okay, okay.
Very cute. Very cute.
いろはちゃん！己もそういうの欲しいなぁ。
Iroha-chan! I want one like that too.
なんかCoolなことやって。
Do something cool.
行きますよ！見てくれるかな？
Here I go! I hope you're watching!
Woah... ぽん！からの、ジャキ！
Woah... pop! And then, Jaki!
Nice Jaki, Jaki!
またつまらぬものを斬ったでござる。
Again, I have cut a worthless object.
Very nice, very nice!
The viewers and audience maybe can tell us
which one was best, but for now,
because I still have many more guests
and many more songs, I have to take this jacket off.
So please... お着替え！Let's go!
So please... Outfit change! Let's go!
隠さなきゃ！キアラ店長を隠せ！
We have to hide her! Hide Kiara-tenchou!
Change, change, change! Don't look! Don't look!
Okay! Wow! Tada! 可愛い！
Okay! Wow! Tada! So cute!
Tada-tada-tada! Thank you, thank you! 可愛い！
Tada-tada-tada! Thank you, thank you! So cute!
So, we already have to say goodbye.
もうバイバイの時間ですね。
It's already time to say bye-bye.
でもありがとう、Thank you!
But thank you, thank you!
楽しかった！またやりましょう！
It was fun! Let's do it again!
次の曲も頑張ってね！
Good luck with the next song too!
頑張ってください！Bye-bye! Bye-bye!
Do your best! Bye-bye! Bye-bye!
Yeah.
Uh-huh.
Can I get-a get-a get all your attention?
I bet you don't know me yet,
君の奥底まで 穿つ目線で
With a gaze that pierces to your very core
溢れる余裕 I'm a mode展開
Overflowing composure, I'm unfolding my mode
Catalyze the noise, go put your hands up
混沌のさなかに 降臨した女神
A goddess who descended into the midst of chaos
I've raised it up, got it ice cold on my body
You wanna know but you don't
進化するセオリー I know
The theory that evolves, I know
I'm a go, I'm a shine shine shine
Can't snap out of my fantasy
Now you see it's interstellar
流されて 飲み込まれる reality
Being swept away, swallowed by reality
Rendez-vous in my universe, come find me now
Hear the voice that’s calling out
まだ見ぬ世界の真髄を 見せてあげるから baby for now
I'll show you the essence of a world yet unseen, baby for now
Calm down let me focus
Under my spell like hypnosis
So don’t get too close when I’m
Come-come-coming through
You wanna roll with me?
We’re taking down yeah
I tell you what to do
I got nothing to prove
Cold when I move when I move when I focus
I tell you what to do
No self-made bulletproof
Cold when I do what I do when I focus
Own me back at my best I finesse what is known
潜む怪物は no secret
The hidden monster is no secret
Listening cool my attitude
Target in my sight locking ready to shot like
Mayday this is an emergency
Working on the pressure baby I can do this in my sleep
世の理だって 書き換えてしまうのよ 夏の when I go
I'll even rewrite the laws of the world in the summer, when I go
When I go I’m a shine shine shine
Won’t stop 煌めく fantasy
Won't stop, sparkling fantasy
Now you see it
銀河を
The galaxy
音色は超 ultra caution
The tone is ultra caution
Rendez-vous in my universe, come find me now
Clear my mind of all this doubt
まだ見ぬ世界の真髄 この目で観たいから baby for now
Because I want to see the essence of a world yet unseen with these eyes, baby for now
Calm down let me focus
Under my spell like hypnosis
So don’t get too close when I’m
Come-come-coming through
You wanna roll with me?
We’re taking down yeah
I tell you what to do
I got nothing to prove
Cold when I move when I move when I focus
I tell you what to do
No self-made bulletproof
Cold when I do what I do when I focus
Oh ma, oh ma, oh ma, oh ma, oh...
垂れる首 don't break my focus
Lower your heads, don't break my focus
Oh ma, oh ma, oh ma, oh ma, oh...
Wanna try and play catch up? Follow my mind
I’m a-get it talk about it loud Can you get it with me now?
宇宙を掌に so on crown Put my feet on the ground
Universe in the palm of my hand so on crown, Put my feet on the ground
任されて配る a piece of cake no stress
Entrusted and handing out, it's a piece of cake, no stress
銀河中魅了して what’s next take a guess yes
Fascinating the entire galaxy, what’s next? Take a guess, yes
I tell you what to do
I got nothing to prove
Cold when I move when I move when I focus
I tell you what to do
No self-made bulletproof
Cold when I do what I do when I focus
Oh ma, oh ma, oh ma, oh ma, oh...
垂れる首 don't break my focus
Lower your heads, don't break my focus
Oh ma, oh ma, oh ma, oh ma, oh...
Wanna try and play catch up? Follow my mind
Focus
Do the best 起こせ 願わくば事故
Do the best, make it happen, hopefully an accident
一世一代 さなぎ落とすジレンマ
Once in a lifetime, the dilemma of shedding the cocoon
勝ち負けとか どうだっていいわ
Winning or losing doesn't really matter
幕開けるわ
The curtain is rising
確信して 勝ちを掴む どちら様 次第次第
Be confident and seize the victory, depending on who you are
引けるか どっから自分 次第次第 なあ
Can you pull back? From where, it depends on yourself, hey
余裕で振り切り 絶好調 絶好調 yeah yeah yeah yeah
Easily shaking it off, in perfect condition, in perfect condition, yeah yeah yeah yeah
そこ退け そこの X 攫うのは私だ
Get out of the way, the one to snatch that X is me
Say more かっさらえ Hey 頂点
Say more, snatch it away, hey, the top
Play boy get don't get in my way じゃあね 黙ってて
Play boy, don't get in my way, see ya, stay quiet
1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3 Sit down, sit down
1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3
ハメ外し気味 ねえ手あげるのは 蘇生か死か
Getting a bit carried away, hey, is raising hands for revival or death?
自画自賛の 小さい才 測れない デタラメ 聖杯 Say goodbye
Self-praising small talent, immeasurable nonsense holy grail, say goodbye
あっちこっち そっちどっち Enough enough 嫌
Here and there, that way or this way, enough, enough, no
満ちなき道よ 闇闇闇
A road without fullness, darkness, darkness, darkness
空回りそうで でもまだ止めないで
Feeling like I'm spinning my wheels, but don't stop yet
あの窓 外声声 それぞれに Get one’s way
Outside that window, voices, voices, each getting their own way
あんたここまで 後ろだけ見て嘆け
This is it for you, just look back and lament
確信して 勝ちを掴む どちら様 次第次第
Be confident and seize the victory, depending on who you are
引けるか どっから自分 次第次第 なあ
Can you pull back? From where, it depends on yourself, hey
余裕で振り切り 絶好調 絶好調 yeah yeah yeah yeah
Easily shaking it off, in perfect condition, in perfect condition, yeah yeah yeah yeah
そこ退け そこの X 攫うのは私だ
Get out of the way, the one to snatch that X is me
Say more かっさらえ Hey 頂点
Say more, snatch it away, hey, the top
Play boy get don't get in my way じゃあね 黙ってて
Play boy, don't get in my way, see ya, stay quiet
黙って
Shut up
1 2 3, 1 2 3, 1 2 3
Sit down, sit down
まさかのバイバイ
An unexpected bye bye
1 2 3, 1 2 3, 1 2 3
Sit down, sit down
I like it, like it, ah
I like him tall, he's my 完璧な規格体
I like him tall, he's my perfect model
FAKE HEART
必要なの ただの person code
All I need is just a person code
甘いフィード 振ってきな 想像通り
A sweet feed, swing it just as imagined
イクぜ Let them all click, need to make it snap down
Here we go, let them all click, need to make it snap down
教えてあげるよ イニシエ Trick
I'll show you, an ancient trick
一, 十, 百 越えりゃ 桃源郷 モバイキョウ
Exceed 1, 10, 100 and it's Xanadu, Mobaikyou
Let them all click, need to make it snap down
Oh my lie 疲れ果てても信じたくない
Oh my lie, even if I'm exhausted I don't want to believe it
Always an ace 僕のためだけ Toy
Always an ace, a toy just for me
愛される覚悟 甘 甘 や 甘
Ready to be loved, sweet sweet, so sweet
Puzzle pieces of love 今
Puzzle pieces of love, now
完璧にフィットする FAKE HEART FAKE HEART
Perfectly hitting, FAKE HEART FAKE HEART
Puzzle pieces of love もっと
Puzzle pieces of love, more
僕の思い通りに Start it up and complete
Just as I planned, start it up and complete
Fake fake FAKE HEART, I like it, like it, ah
Fake fake でも バラバラ
Fake fake but falling apart
何度もリスタート Perfect is my target
Restarting again and again, perfect is my target
What's the matter? Pop pop the matter
やり合い 世界 変えてゆきましょう
Let's keep changing this competitive world
コグニティブ 誰も彼も みんな
Cognitive, everyone and anyone
リセットするから Boom boom boom
Because I'll reset it, boom boom boom
ようこそ僕の Playground 未来の展示会さ
Welcome to my playground, it's a future exhibition
100%満足 約束しますカラー
I promise 100% satisfaction, in color
有意的とか 時代遅れ 付いてきなよなクバのラブ
Meaningful or obsolete, keep up with the Cuba's love
聞くなら 上手 残念 執着したい君の
If you listen, skillfully, unfortunately, I want to obsess over you
Oh my lie 疲れ果てても信じたくない
Oh my lie, even if I'm exhausted I don't want to believe it
Always an ace 僕のためだけ Toy
Always an ace, a toy just for me
愛される覚悟 甘 甘 や 甘
Ready to be loved, sweet sweet, so sweet
Puzzle pieces of love 今
Puzzle pieces of love, now
完璧にフィットする FAKE HEART FAKE HEART
Perfectly hitting, FAKE HEART FAKE HEART
Puzzle pieces of love もっと
Puzzle pieces of love, more
僕の思い通りに Start it up and complete
Just as I planned, start it up and complete
Fake fake FAKE HEART, I like it, like it, ah
Fake fake でも バラバラ
Fake fake but falling apart
何度もリスタート Perfect is my target
Restarting again and again, perfect is my target
夢か 現実か どっちでもいい
Dream or reality, either is fine
ビジョンに 行きたい Oh yeah
I want to go into the vision, oh yeah
恐怖のクレーン プログラム プログラム
Fearful crane, program program
実現まで急ぐ 命は 短し
Rushing to realization, life is short
Pomp! Again! Yeah!
何が悪いわけ？
What's wrong with that?
Puzzle pieces of love 今
Puzzle pieces of love, now
完璧にフィットする FAKE HEART FAKE HEART
Perfectly hitting, FAKE HEART FAKE HEART
Puzzle pieces of love もっと
Puzzle pieces of love, more
僕の思い通りに Start it up and complete
Just as I planned, start it up and complete
Follow follow, like it, like it, 描く人生はフィクション
Follow follow, like it, like it, the life I draw is fiction
Follow follow, like it, like it, さぁどうぞ入厩を
Follow follow, like it, like it, now please join the stable
Follow follow, like it, like it, 編み出せよ 最後
Follow follow, like it, like it, weave it until the end
パラバラ Like it, like it, 楽しんで
Scattered like it, like it, have fun
フィーリンググラデーション
Feeling Gradation
Uh...
My heart starts skipping a bit
今 踊りだシーンショー
Now, let's start the dance scene show
様変わりして Show time
A complete change, it's show time
全然悪くない Imagination
Not bad at all, imagination
視界の霧は晴れ渡って
The mist in my sight has cleared up
悲しみに別れを告げる
Bidding farewell to sadness
すいま まい まつり 掘り出して
Sleepiness and dance festival, dig it out
にじむ...
Blurring...
Lalaink wa balailo
どれだけ上手く見せようとしても
No matter how well I try to act
君がいなければ何の意味もない
It means nothing without you
かすり傷すらつかない幻想
An illusion without even a scratch
針の落ちないレコードさ
Like a record whose needle won't drop
たった今 留め処ない追い風背にして
Right now, with an endless tailwind at my back
Come as flow
吹き荒れる向かい風にも心 なびかせて
Letting my heart flutter even in the raging headwind
飛び乗って to the future
Jump on into the future
ライン引いたって Are We Start Line?
Even if we draw a line, are we at the start line?
ときめいてしまえば
If our hearts start to throb
瞬く間に広がる開放
Liberation spreads in the blink of an eye
一挙手一投足すべてがドラマ
Every move and every gesture is a drama
待ちわびたデーブレイク Are We Start Line?
代わる代わる彩るパノラマ
満ち溢れる フィーリングラデーション
The long-awaited daybreak, are we at the start line?
A panorama colored in turn
Overflowing with Feeling Gradation
始まりのその時が来た
The time for the beginning has come
Nothing is impossible
紛い物 騙し効かない世界
In a world where fakes and deception don't work
この先はまだ誰も知らない世界
The world ahead that no one knows yet
呆感してるだけじゃ味気ない
Just being in a daze is tasteless
リアルタイムで 通じ合って
Connecting in real time
ふり幅 限界モーション
The width of the swing, limit motion
徒労に終わらせない Idol mind
I won't let it end in vain, Idol mind
感情的なシチュエーション
An emotional situation
行けるどこまで行ってみよう
Let's see how far we can go
選択肢にない Get a whole new way
There's no other choice, get a whole new way
共に声を鳴らせ
Let's raise our voices together
素肌を貫くような真っ直ぐな痛みが
Even if a straight pain that pierces the skin...
伴っても
...accompanies it
この仲間たちと最果てまで
With these friends until the very end
Keep running to the end
飛び乗って to the future
Jump on into the future
ライン引いたって Are We Start Line?
Even if we draw a line, are we at the start line?
ときめいてしまえば
If our hearts start to throb
瞬く間に広がる開放
Liberation spreads in the blink of an eye
一挙手一投足すべてがドラマ
Every move and every gesture is a drama
待ちわびたデーブレイク Are We Start Line?
The long-awaited daybreak, are we at the start line?
代わる代わる彩るパノラマ
A panorama colored in turn
満ち溢れる フィーリングラデーション
Overflowing with Feeling Gradation
躍り出せ You raise me up
Dance out, you raise me up
恐れるものはない Are We Start Line?
There's nothing to fear, are we at the start line?
綺麗な最果てが
The beautiful ultimate end...
不透明な明日を照らすよ
...will illuminate the opaque tomorrow
Are We Start Line?
Are we at the start line?
Kiara-senpai, Happy Birthday!
Thank you, thank you! Well, all you wished me happy birthday,
but since we went to Austria together...
...can you say it in German? Happy Birthday?
Sure! Sure, sure! Oh, German!
Okay, I teach you, I teach you. Oh, you don't know, right?
I don't know, sorry.
教えてくれるんだ、よかった。
You're gonna teach us? Great.
Yeah. It's "Alles Gute..."
Alles Gute!
Gute? Gute!
Alles Gute! Alles Gute!
Zum... Geburtstag!
Geburtstag! Oh! Perfect! Okay!
せーの！
Alles Gute zum Geburtstag!
Ready, set...
Yay! 嬉しい！もはやドイツかオーストリア人。やったー！
Yay! I'm happy! You're basically German or Austrian now. We did it!
Thank you! Super danke! Super danke! Super danke!
Thank you! Thanks a lot! Thanks a lot! Thanks a lot!
Okay! Self-introduction in English! Okay! From who?
Ririka!
Hi! Hello everyone! Kawaii positive energy genius!
I'm Ichijou Ririka from Hololive DEV_IS ReGLOSS. Nice to meet you!
And next!
Hello everyone!
はーい、儒烏風亭らでん、フロムホロライブデバイス、ReGLOSS！イエーイ！
Hi, I'm Juufuutei Raden from hololive DEV_IS, ReGLOSS! Yay!
イエーイ！
Yay!
ペラペラ、ペラペラ、ペラペラ
Pera pera, pera pera, pera pera
Okay, everyone, we danced your song together! Yay!
Thank you! Oh, thank you!
I'm so happy! Feeling Gradation!
Awesome! I- I felt- I'm feeling very happy
to be able to dance this song 'cause it's so cool! めっちゃかっこいい曲！
to be able to dance this song 'cause it's so cool! It's such a cool song!
やったー！
We did it!
But how was it to dance with, like, a non-ReGLOSS member?
It's actually first time to dance together,
who is not ReGLOSS member, so I was a little bit nervous, but...
Finally, we can do it! Yay! Heart-warming!
I think, you know, I chose the white version
of this outfit because I thought we'd look so good together.
Suits on you! Yay!
So, because we look so good together, let's take a cute picture, okay?
Okay! Okay! Yay!
Strike a pose!
Wait, I- I will go like here.
No, closer, closer, closer, closer! Okay!
ニャア！
Nyaa!
Yay! Screenshot! Screenshot!
Feeling Gradation!
やったー！
Yay!
Okay! Yay! Woo!
Thank you, thank you! I had so much fun! Dankeschön!
Me too! Dankeschön! Super danke! Super danke! Dankeschön!
じゃあ、えー、Feeling Gradationを、ReGLOSSのこの可愛いお二人と一緒に踊りましたけども...
So, we just danced "Feeling Gradation" with these two cute girls from ReGLOSS, but...
I have even more guests coming! And even more songs coming!
And for that, I will go to the center stage.
おー、先輩カッコいい！ オッケー！ またねー！
Oh, Senpai is so cool! Okay! See you!
バイバイ！ スーパーダンケ！ スーパーダンケ！
Bye bye! Super danke! Super danke!
頑張れ、頑張れー！
Good luck, good luck!
帰ろー。ンデランダランダランダラン...
Let's go home. Nderan daran daran daran...
デア・エア・デア・エア　孤独待ち合って
De-A-E-A, De-A-E-A, waiting for each other in solitude
祝えば宴　大胆な幕開け
If we celebrate, it's a banquet, a bold beginning
つまらない　下らない　なら　Death, death, death
If it's boring or trivial, then Death, death, death
ありきたりな毎日　ちょっと抜け出し　ハイ！
Breaking away a bit from the ordinary everyday, hi!
欲してんのは最新型の上々
What I want is the latest superb state
そんでもって無限永久の頂上
And then, the infinite and eternal peak
ちょっと待ってちょっとジャン　今行けるだろう？
Wait a second, wait a bit, we can go now, right?
愛してバースデイ
Love me, it's my birthday
ドゥワッパー　ときめきにネバーギブアップ
Du-whappa, never give up on the excitement
連れ出して　連れ出して　その歌で
Take me out, take me out with that song
ハッピーバースデイ
Happy birthday
そんなんな　僕らが出会えば
If we meet like that
特別映えるワンシーン
A particularly standout scene
目出度い祝いへ
To the joyous celebration
解けたアシュレース　皆押して
Untied shoelaces, everyone push forward
未知なき未知へ　永久不白 Never never
To the pathless unknown, eternally unpainted, Never never
なるようになっていく魔法が公開中
The magic of things turning out as they should is being revealed
不敗だも　自己流　踊り出す宇宙
Even if undefeated, it's my own style, the universe starts dancing
掛けてるどこか　ボルテージ
A voltage missing somewhere
オーナナ　涙お見通しだ
Oh-na-na, I see right through the tears
その分だけ星になれ　煌めいて
Become stars for that amount, and sparkle
ドゥワッパー　胸騒ぎが震えて
Du-whappa, the unease is trembling
あの日にかけた魔法が　今だ解けない
The magic cast that day still hasn't worn off
愛してバースデイ
Love me, it's my birthday
一息超えた　夢の踊り場
A dream's landing after catching a breath
堪えられさ　答えなんかきっと
I can endure it, for the answer is surely...
観点外外　ベイビー
Out of sight, baby
超絶歴史　今の我々
Superb history, the us of now
私の運命　絶景
My fate is a magnificent view
ドゥワッパー　僕たちはネバーギブアップ
Du-whappa, we will never give up
踊らせて　踊らせて　その歌で
Let us dance, let us dance to that song
ハッピーバースデイ
Happy birthday
嗚呼、嗚呼、朝を見つけた
Ah, ah, I've found the morning
瞬き色めく世界へ
Into a world sparkling in a blink
愛してバースデイ　イェイ！
Love me, it's my birthday, yay!
嗚呼...
Ah...
今響くこの響きは変わらずに
This resonance ringing now remains unchanged
合図はここから君に通知
A signal sent to you from here
愛してるよ　ずっと　ハッピーバースデイ僕らへ
I love you, forever, happy birthday to us
I love you all, lucky us babe
照らして
Shine on us
Lucky us babe, 祝おうか
Lucky us babe, shall we celebrate?
手、上げな！
Put your hands up!
愛してバースデイ
Love me, it's my birthday
Let me know...
どこで
Where...
どんな
What kind of...
景色
scenery...
見てる
...are you seeing?
君に
Continuing...
続け
...on to you,
at anything anywhere.
DISTANCE
Lyrics: Ryosuke Imai Music: Ryosuke Imai / Tasuku Maeda
この地図の指し示す方へ
Toward the direction shown on this map,
君の足跡たどりながら
While tracing your footsteps.
憧れを力に変えて
Turning my admiration into strength,
Rock my world, baby.
あれからどれくらい
How much since then...
君に追いつけたんだろう
...have I managed to catch up to you?
いつでも前を行く
Always going ahead of me,
その背中を見つめ続けてきた
I've kept staring at your back.
遠い道のり
The long journey...
超えていくたびに
...every time I overcome it,
本当の強さの意味を知るから
Because I learn the meaning of true strength.
全てを投げ出したとしてもまだ
Even if I threw everything away,
君との距離感詰めきれなくて
I still couldn't close the distance between us.
あの日々 あの時 思い起こせば
When I recall those days, that time...
この想いを届け
Deliver these feelings!
どこで
Where...
どんな
What kind of...
景色
scenery...
見てる
...are you seeing?
君に
Continuing...
続け
...on to you,
at anything anywhere.
いつかは誰かが
Maybe someday someone...
私の背中を追うようになるかも
...will start chasing after my back.
Run to you, baby.
それでもペースは落とさずに
Even so, without slowing my pace,
振り返らずに
Without looking back,
ゴールを目指し走ってく
I'll keep running towards the goal.
いつも自分がいた時の上にいることだけ
Believing only that I am above where I used to be,
信じて
I'll believe.
たとえ何度も
Even if many times...
壁を感じても
...I feel the walls,
茨の道を乗り越えてみせる
I'll show you I can overcome the thorny path.
全てを投げ出したとしてもまだ
Even if I threw everything away,
君との距離感詰めきれなくて
I still couldn't close the distance between us.
あの日々 あの時 思い起こせば
When I recall those days, that time...
この想いを届け
Deliver these feelings!
どこで
Where...
どんな
What kind of...
景色
scenery...
見てる
...are you seeing?
君に
Continuing...
続け
...on to you,
at anything anywhere.
また君と会える日を信じて
Believing in the day I can meet you again,
受け止めた想いを未来へと
The feelings I've received, towards the future...
届けるのさ
...I will deliver them.
全てを投げ出したとしてもまだ
Even if I threw everything away,
君との距離感詰めきれなくて
I still couldn't close the distance between us.
あの日々 あの時 思い起こせば
When I recall those days, that time...
この想いを届け
Deliver these feelings!
どこで
Where...
どんな
What kind of...
景色
scenery...
見てる
...are you seeing?
君に
Continuing...
続け
...on to you,
at anything anywhere.
Let me know...
レディーマーメイド
Lyrics: 桑村 憲代 Music: 大坪 直樹
Lady Mermaid
Lyrics: Noriyo Kuwamura Music: Naoki Otsubo
One for the one
海岸沿い
Along the coast,
退屈な奴らが集まる
where boring people gather,
あの店 二人のステージ
at that shop, it's our stage.
ふたごみたいね
We're like twins, aren't we?
ばっちり睫毛は今日も
With perfect eyelashes today, too,
潮風 受け止めているわ
we're taking in the sea breeze.
二人が
When the two of us...
踊りだしたら ほら
...start dancing, look!
誰にも 負けないわ
We won't lose to anyone!
Step, baby.
Let's dance tonight
海岸通りの噂　私達のものなの
The rumors along the coastal road belong to us
虜にするわ　逃がさない
I'll captivate you and never let you go
Come on Come on Come on my darling
渚に踊る
Dancing on the beach
君と私は
you and I
今も昔も　レディーマーメイド
Now and then, we're Lady Mermaids
Hey boy (hoo!)
恋も車も
Both love and cars
夏は渋滞さ
are in a traffic jam in summer
人魚の恋はね
A mermaid's love is
儚いものなの
a fleeting thing
泣いて笑ったね
We cried and laughed
End of the summer
One for the one
ああ　避暑地の景色は変わってゆくさ
Ah, the scenery of the summer resort keeps changing
二人は変わらないけど
but the two of us remain the same
ああ　コンクリートに消えたくなる砂浜
Ah, the sandy beach that wants to disappear into concrete
なんだか切なくなるね
makes me feel somewhat lonely
君が街を飛び出してさ
You left the city
夢と共に暮らした
and lived with your dreams
City my life my way
都会の匂い憧れ
Longing for the city's scent
君がいなくなったの
you were gone
二人の海は
Our sea
冷たすぎて
was too cold
Get back Get back Get back my friend
海辺の街で
In the seaside town
二人で一つ
we were as one
ずっと前から　一緒さ
We've been together for a long time
Hey girl (hoo!)
秋が来たなら　潮が引くように
When autumn comes, just as the tide recedes
夢も車も　なくなるのかね
will the dreams and cars disappear too?
海岸通りを
Let's speed along
飛ばそうぜ
the coastal road
渚に踊る
Dancing on the beach
君と私は
you and I
今も昔も　レディーマーメイド
Now and then, we're Lady Mermaids
Hey boy (hoo!)
恋も車も
Both love and cars
夏は渋滞さ
are in a traffic jam in summer
ひと夏の夢と
Even if we try to run through
駆け抜けてみても
a single summer's dream
二人で泣いてた
we were crying together
End of the summer
海辺の街で
In the seaside town
二人で一つ
we were as one
ずっと前から　一緒さ
We've been together for a long time
Hey girl (hoo!)
冬の潮風
If the winter sea breeze
頬を突き刺せば
stings our cheeks
季節外れの
out-of-season
レディーマーメイド
Lady Mermaids
泣いて笑ったね
We cried and laughed
End of the summer
海岸通りを
Let's speed along
飛ばそうぜ
the coastal road
One for the one
やった！ We did it! We did it!
We did it! We did it! We did it!
Okay, let's start right ahead with an introduction!
Hello everybody!
My name is Mint Fantome.
I am a ghost maid VTuber.
I'm not a part of Hololive, but I am a big fan of
Miss Takanashi Kiara!
Yeah! It is our first ever 3D appearance
together!
Together!
And we sang a beautiful song that I think
means a lot to both of us!
To both of us! Mmm!
What's it called? It was...
Lady Mermaid!
From... some two beautiful ladies from Hello Project,
Suzuki Airi and Sugaya Risako,
who by now you guys should really
remember those names!
...at the Easter live that I had, okay?
Yeah, yeah, yeah. So it's 'Hell Project' all over again.
We had a lot of fun with that, right?
We did!
Practicing together...
Oh my gosh!
...shaking the booty!
When we were doing practice, every time we would like do the...
...this part, we would stare at each other...
...looking at me! Shaking the booty! Woooo!
So fun! Yeah!
I'm so happy that we're together...
Me too!
...and you're here!
I know!
It's like... it's like... honestly, it really does feel like this is a different timeline...
...where somehow you ended up here!
Oh! Yeah!
Maybe!
It's kind of fun to like... today I'm roleplaying!
Yeah, yeah! A little bit!
Ooh, I wonder which generation you're from if you're roleplaying!
Oh!
And then I also got to see the big wall of the signatures and everything!
Oh, the signatures!
Yeah, it's been really exciting being here at the Hololive Studio!
So thank you everybody!
Thank you, Kiara-sama!
Thank you for having me!
Yeah, it's my first time having an external guest, so that's exciting!
Really?
Yeah!
Wow!
Yeah, I've been like kind of trying to get something going for a while, but it finally worked out!
But now finally you're ready!
Like, I was gonna like honestly invite you earlier, but you know, it took you a while to...
...become this!
I feel... I feel too honored for this!
I feel like I'm too small for this position!
I feel... (whining sounds)
Okay, okay. So anyway...
This was a special time, but so...
...fact is, fact of the matter is, you are a maid!
Yes!
And you have to like kind of pay for this exposure I've given you!
Oh! Uh...
So I would like you to clean the stage, please, 'cause there's dirt, dirt, dirt, dirt!
Oh! Oh! Get rid of it!
Where did this come from?
You're a maid, right? Clean it up!
Uh, I have no materials! I'll just use my hands!
(grunting sounds of cleaning)
Why is it not going away?
(more grunting/struggling sounds)
You're so bad at this!
I'm sorry, お嬢様! Goddammit!
I'm sorry, mistress! Goddammit!
Let me kiss your feet!
You better!
All the KFP are crying right now!
Get to work!
(kissing sounds)
It's not going away!
Mamma mia! Oh my god! Can you not do anything right?
I'm sorry, お嬢様! Please forgive me! Don't kick me out!
I'm sorry, mistress! Please forgive me! Don't kick me out!
No! I will not forgive you! I will show you how it's done!
Okay!
Yeah!
(screams and starts chasing Cecilia with a frying pan)
You know what? I am going to get you!
(Kiara chasing Cecilia, both screaming)
Turn it up to the top, let's get it started go non-stop
Bust through the door, we don't knock (it's time to go non-stop)
Like we never cared about what they say, tear up the place like it's our own
Wilder than a cyclone and leave it on a high note
And it's just like magic, lighting up the sky, yeah
When we're together we don't have to try
If you wanna join then this is your invite
Show what you got, come on don't be shy
We, we are breaking through borders
Free, like the clouds are beneath us
Oh we, we're like diamonds in starlight
We shine in the dark night 'cause we are the highlight
We, we're just living this moment
Free, on this path that we've chosen
Oh we, we're like diamonds in starlight
We shine in the dark night 'cause we are the highlight
Hands up above our heads, it's time to make it pop (la la la)
Keep this belief until we lose control, it's in your blood
You know there ain't no pomp or body getting down like we do
There ain't no pomp or body like a party with me, go
And it's just like magic, lighting up the sky, yeah
When we're together we don't have to try
If you wanna join then this is your invite
Show what you got, come on don't be shy
We, we are breaking through borders
Free, like the clouds are beneath us
Oh we, we're like diamonds in starlight
We shine in the dark night 'cause we are the highlight
We, we're just living this moment
Free, on this path that we've chosen and we...
We're like diamonds in starlight,
we shine in the dark night
'cause we are the highlight.
Don't lose your dream, make it reality, baby
don't lose your dream, make it...
Now everybody let me hear you say!
Don't lose your dream, go and make it for real, baby
don't lose your dream.
Free,
we are breaking through borders,
free,
like nobody can stop us, oh we
are diamonds in starlight,
'cause you know that we are...
We are, we are breaking through borders,
free,
like the stars are beneath us, oh we
are, we're like diamonds in starlight,
we shine in the dark night
'cause we are the highlight.
Free,
we're just living this moment,
free,
on this path that we've chosen and we,
we're like diamonds in starlight,
we shine in the dark night
'cause we are the highlight.
Highlight, highlight, highlight, highlight.
Highlight, highlight, highlight, yay!
That was another banger from Kiara and I did it
with all my beloved ID girls.
I love you, I love you ID girls, I love you so much!
Yes, so after this wonderful banger, as you may have
noticed, if you look at the time,
it might be time to end soon and therefore I will
introduce some merchandise to you guys.
It's birthday merchandise time!
ではでは誕生日記念のグッズ出るので紹介したいと思います。
Well then, birthday commemoration goods are coming
out, so I'd like to introduce them.
どうぞ見ていきましょう。
Please, let's take a look.
Let's check it out!
That is the overview.
And now let me show you all of them in detail.
First of all, the tapestry! Ta-da!
As you can tell, I am in a wedding dress!
なんと、なんと私、なんか可愛い服着てますね。
Wha- wha-, I'm wearing some cute clothes,
aren't I?
ああ、恥ずかしい。
Ah, how embarrassing.
Yeah, um, it's about time right? I don't know.
It's a beautiful tapestry, I haven't done a tapestry
in a while so I thought you guys deserved one.
And next, with the same beautiful face and a
different expression perhaps, it will be a little badge.
So if you are a badge collector, now's the time!
If you have an itabag or something to fill up, now's
the time to get yourself a wawa badge, a wawawaifu badge!
Oh, and by the way, the illustration is by DOTORI.
Thank you so much, it's so beautiful, I look so cute.
バッジ集めてる人もぜひ今回、どうぞいっぱい買ってください。
Those who collect badges too, please do buy
many this time.
ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much.
And next up is the lamp! Yeah!
The title is: "You Light Up My Life Lamp".
You! Because it's a chicken, it's a KFP chicken!
はい、私の人生を照らしてくれるのがあなたなので、その姿をしたランプでございます。
Yes, because you are the one who lights up
my life, it's a lamp in that form.
And next we have the "Anger Management Frog Ball"!
Froggy wawa!
Perfect right? You want to squeeze it and squish
her head, don't you? Me too!
おこ、おこ、おこマネジメント、え、カエルボールでございます。
Oko-, oko-, oko- management, uh, frog ball.
フロギーわわの顔付いてるボールです。とてもキュートですけど、
It's a ball with Froggy Wawa's face on it.
It's very cute, but...
何かね、押したいんだよね、うん。
you know, you want to press it, yeah.
And next we have a situational voice! Yes!
It is matching with the tapestry actually.
So this, it fits you know, like this whole
honeymoon wedding situation.
I normally don't really go that hard on the romance in my
voice packs so it's a very big... just this time, just this once.
ちょっとだけ...
Just a little...
えー、ちょっと恥ずかしい、
Um, it's a bit embarrassing,
ロマンチックなシチュエーションです。
it's a romantic situation.
タペストリーに合わせてます。
It matches the tapestry.
日本語もあります。よかったらどうぞ。
There's a Japanese version too. Check it out.
キア！
Kya!
And for the full set, if you want the full set, you will get a postcard
extra, and a limited amount will be signed by me with my hand
and the rest will be stamped.
数量限定は私のサインが入るポストカードが特典になっています。
The limited quantity set comes with a postcard signed by me as a bonus.
で、その他はスタンプです。
And the rest are stamped.
And another special bonus if you get the full set is a Hololive card!
Special Hololive card! Yeah! This can be used in the Hololive Official Card Game,
but you have to purchase the full set through the official website, Geek Jack, or any others are not possible.
If you want to learn how to play, please check out the Hololive Official Card Game website! Yeah!
タレントプレミアムグッズのフルセット特典としてもう一つ追加。
One more addition as a full set bonus for the talent premium goods.
このカードが付いてきます。はい。
This card is included. Yes.
ちゃんと Hololive Official Card Game で使用できます！やったー！
You can actually use it in the Hololive Official Card Game! Yay!
えーと、カードの詳細は Hololive Official Card Game の公式ホームページにて確認してください。
Um, please check the official Hololive Official Card Game website for card details.
イェイイェイナイス！特典が二つ。
Yay, yay, nice! Two bonuses.
And next, after all this merch announcement,
let me just tell you that the merch will be, you know, you can get it
after the next song because the next song will be
my next original song and it's called TASTY.
チャチャン！
Ta-da!
Yes, TASTY is the name of my next original song
and it will start being released on all streaming services
at midnight your time. Whatever your time zone is, it will be up on midnight.
But the music video will come up right after this,
we're raiding into it unless it doesn't work, but we're raiding into it
and you will see the music video and after the music video
the merch will be available at the 10 minute mark of whatever hour you are in. Okay?
私の新曲です！やったー！TASTYでございます！
It's my new song! Yay! It's called TASTY!
このあと披露しますし、このあとMVも公開されます！
I'll perform it now, and the MV will be released afterwards!
そのあとにグッズも出ます！
The merch will come out after that!
よろしくお願いします！フー！
Please look forward to it! Woo!
So with that, it is finally time for the last song of my birthday live
and my new original song. So please listen to TASTY.
Tasty, tasty, yeah
Tasty, tasty
Tongue tied, oh you don't gotta hide it
Obvious I get you excited
Don't want perfume on my skin, just need you, yeah
Sugary thoughts, nah I don't mind it
Confection affection, it feels right
Flavor makes you go...
No beggin' needed, just take a bite
Lemme show you what I can take, make ache
I'll make you feel like you're alive
Alive, alive, feel your heartbeat
Honey drippin', you see what we've done tonight
Just a little taste of me
Sweet like sugar, rotten down to the core
Savor every little taste, give you more
Flavored hard candy, addictive, so sweet
You got me like that, that, that, that
T-taste me, gettin' every drop
You know you like it a lot, you know I'm taste-taste-taste-taste-tasty
Taste me, tell me what do you want
I'll be your la-lollipop, you know I'm taste-taste-taste-taste-tasty
Baby look at my picture, know you wanna be my mister, mister
I can be a little bitter, switch up, whimper, worship me like I'm scripture
This sickly sweet candied love
Makes you want more, mm wow, are you satisfied now?
Hear you say you want me
Can't stop the way your eyes wander, oh
So dolce
Lemme show you what I can take, make ache
I'll make you feel like you're alive
Alive, alive, feel your heartbeat
Honey drippin', you see what we've done tonight
Just a little taste of me
Sweet like sugar, rotten down to the core
Savor every little taste, give you more
Flavored hard candy, addictive, so sweet
You got me like that
That that that that
Ooh
Sweet aroma
Got us both actin' up tonight, tonight
Ooh
Sugar coma
Fall into me you want it oh no
Baby, I'm sweet for you
I'ma keep it tasty, tasty
Know you like this taste, taste, taste
T-taste me
Gettin' every drop
You know you like it a lot
You know I'm taste-taste-taste-tasty
Taste me
Tell me what do you want!
I'll be your la-lollipop
You know I'm taste-taste-taste-tasty
So sweet, not enough of me
Drippin' sugary, just for you
Taste-taste-taste-tasty
So sweet, got a crush on me
Sugar rush right into you
Taste-taste-taste-tasty
Not enough of me
Drippin'-
Taste-taste-taste-taste-taste-taste-tasty
So sweet, got a crush on me
Sugar rush
Taste-taste-taste-tasty
CAST: Takanashi Kiara
Hoshimachi Suisei
Momosuzu Nene
La+ Darknesss
Kazama Iroha
SPECIAL THANKS: 合同会社 VESSEL LIFE
SPECIAL THANKS: VESSEL LIFE LLC